Guide to the University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg, Subject Files, 1963-present UPG.RG.52
ULS Greensburg
- Chancellor's Distinguished Teaching Award [Chancellor's Award for Distinguished Teaching], 1986-present (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 2)
  1986 Dr. Diane Marsh, Professor of Psychology 1989 Dr. Nancy Estrada, Assistant Prof. of Hispanic Languages and Literature 1990 Dr. Ted Zaleskiewicz, Professor of Physics 1992 Assoc. Prof. Judith Vollmer, Assoc. Professor of English and Writing Program Director 1994 Dr. Mark McColloch, Assoc. Professor of History 1996 Dr. Anthony Boldurian, Assoc. Professor of Anthropology 1997 Dr. Lillian Beeson, Assoc. Professor of Communication 1999 Dr. Richard Blevins, Assoc. Professor of English 2000 Prof. Joanne J. Viano, Asst. Professor of French 2002 Dr. Mary Beth Spore, Asst. Prof. of English 2002 Dr. Walter Orange, Asst. Prof. of Mathematics 2004 Assoc. Prof., Stephen Murabito, Assoc. Prof. of English 2011 Dr. Matthew Luderer, Assoc. Prof. of Chemistry 2014 Dr. Sayre Greenfield, Prof. of English 2015 Dr. William Pamerleau 2017 Dr. Melissa J. Marks 2019 Barnhart, Barbara, Instructor in Biology
- Cheerleaders [University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg Cheerleaders], 1969-1970 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 2)
  First team of Cheerleaders, 1969/70: Linda Adams, Karen Battistoni, Joan Boby, Donna DiMaria, Diane Kosic (News article with newspaper photo in Basketball (Men's) Scrapbook –Basketball (Men's), 1969/70.)
  See UPG.RG.60 Visual Images. Ser.: Prints – Cheerleaders.
- Children's Literature Conference (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 2)
  See: UPG.RG.52 Subject Files. Ser.: Events (Campus Sponsored)
  For photographs, See: UPG.RG.60 Visual Images. Prints. Children's Literature Conference.
- Circle Dinner [President's Fall Reception for Faculty and Staff] (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 2)
  See: UPG.RG.02.4 Ser.: Memoranda. See: UPG.RG.02.5 Ser.: Memoranda. See: UPG.RG.60 Prints – President's Fall Reception for Faculty and Staff.
- CLICK (Computer Literacy Initiative for Community Kids) (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 2)
- Cobetto Lecture Series [Dr. Bernard H. Cobetto Lecture Series; The Dr. Bernard Cobetto Lecture Series on Contemporary Ethical Issues], 2006-present (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 3, Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  Historical Note: Contents: Drafts of a proposal entitled, "Contemporary Ethical Issues", prepared by Dr. William Rued and Dr. William Pamerleau, UPG Professors of Philosophy; ltr dtd 9/19/2004, Dr. Frank A. Cassell to Dr. Bernard H. Cobetto, transmitting copy of the Rued/Pamerleau proposal to Dr. Cobetto; memo 9/22/2004 FAC to Drs. Rued, Pamerleau, Subj.: "acceptance and support" of the proposal by Dr. Cobetto with an endowment of $100,000 to the UPG Foundation to support "The Dr. Bernard Cobetto Lecture Series [The Dr. Bernard Cobetto Lecture Series on Contemporary Ethical Issues]"; ltr dtd 6/28/2005 Chancellor Mark A. Nordenberg to Dr. Cobetto acknowledging the endowment; Inaugural lecture given Feb. 13, 2006; includes a Status Report of the endowment as of 6/30/2005.
  1st annual lecture, Feb. 23, 2006, Randy Cohen, "How to Be Good". [No DVD of this lecture in the Archives]
  2nd annual lecture, Apr. 4, 2007, Dr. James Childress, "Just Care: Rationing in a Public Health Care Crisis". [For DVD, See: UPG.RG.60 DVD17, Cobetto Lecture Series, 2007 (2nd)].
  3rd annual lecture, Apr. 11, 2008, Dr. Everette E. Dennis, "Trusting the Media in a Presidential Year: Can We or Not -- A Look at Freedom of the Press in the Digital Age." [No DVD of this lecture in the Archives]
  4th annual lecture, Mar. 24, 2009, Dr. Barbara M. Porco, "Ethical Leadership: The "Tipping Point in a Financial Crisis." [For DVD, See: UPG.RG.60 DVD17, Cobetto Lecture Series, 2009 (4th)].
  5th annual lecture, Apr. 13, 2010, Paul H. O'Neil, "The Role of a Leader in Creating a Values-Based Institution". [For DVD, See: UPG.RG.60 DVD17, Cobetto Lecture Series, 2010 (5th)].
  6th annual lecture, Apr. 14, 2011, Dr. Bernard Duberstein, "Leadership Lessons from the Oval Office and the Board Room". [For DVD, See: UPG.RG.60 DVD17 Cobetto Lecture Series. 2011 (6th).]
  7th annual lecture, Apr. 3, 2012. Dr. John E. Abraham, "Madmen, Educats, and Demagogues: Confessions of a Recovering Politician." [For DVD, See: UPG.RG.60 DVD21 Cobetto Lecture Series, 2012 (7th).]
  8th annual lecture, Apr. 10, 2013. Dr. Wendy Lynne Lee, "When the Earth Moves Under Our Feet: The Pennsylvania Marcellus Gas Rush." [For DVD, See: UPG.RG.60 DVD 17, Cobetto Lecture Series, 2013 (8th)
  9th annual lecture, Apr. 8, 2014, "End-of-Life-Care Issues", A Panel discussion featuring: Robert Arnold, MD; Helen Burns, PhD, RN, FAAN; John Dickson IV, Alan Meisel, Esq. [For DVD, See UPG.RG.60 DVD17 Cobetto Lecture Series, 2014 (9th).]
  10th annual lecture, Apr. 16, 2015. Dr. William A. Rued, "Toward an Ethics of Love and Hope: Five Transformative Ideas." [For DVD, See UPG.RG.60 DVD17 Cobetto Lecture Series, 2015 (10th).]
  11th annual lecture, Apr. 13, 2016. Joanne Katz, JD, "Restorative Justice: Exploring Ethics and Criminal Justice in the Age of Mass Incarceration." [No DVD of this lecture in the Archives]
  12th annual lecture, Apr. 12, 2017. William Chess, retired COO, Ogilvy Public Relations World. Topic: "Public Relations: Public Policy and Crisis Communications in a World That Relies on Social Media." [For DVD, See: UPG.RG.60 DVD17 Cobetto Lecture Series, 2017 (12th)]
  13th annual lecture, Apr. 5, 2018. Panel discussion with: Hon. John J. Driscoll, senior judge Family Court Division, Westmorelend County Court of Common Pleas; Ann M. Emmerling, Blackburn Center (Greensburg, Pa.); David Karp, Prof. of Sociology, Director of Project on Restorative Justice, Skidmore College; and Kate Pope, Title IX Coordinator, University of Pittsburgh. Topic: "Sexual Misconduct: Perspectives on the Problem, Possibilities for Resolution." Thursday, April 5, 7 p.m., University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg, Ferguson Theater, Smith Hall. [No DVD of this lecture in the Archives]
  14th annual lecture, Apr. 16, 2019. "Climate Change & Its Effect on Western Pennsylvania", a panel discussion with: Richard Alley, PhD, Evan Pugh, University Professor of Geoscience, Penn State; Ines M. L. Azevedo, PhD, Professor, Dept. of Engineering and Public Policy, Carnegie Mellon University and Co-Director, Climate and Energy Decision Making Center; Grant Ervin, Chief Resillience Officer/Asst. Director, Dept. of City Planning, City of Pittsburgh; Barry Kukovich, Director of Community Relations, Peoples Gas Company (Pittsburgh); V. Kerry Smith (moderator)—Emeritus Regents Professor and Emeritus University Professor of Economics, as well as a distinguished Sustainability Scientist in GIOS, Arizona State University. [For DVD, See: UPG.RG.60 DVD17 Cobetto Lecture Series, 2019 (14th)]
  15th annual lecture, Sept. 28, 2022. Michael P. Colaresi, PhD, the William S. Dietrich II Professor of Political Science and Research and Academic Director for Pitt Cyber, "The Earth is Flat (On Our Screens): How Democracy is Disrupted by Disinformation and Digital Illusions of Information and Control".
  See Also: UPG.RG.60 DVD
- CLIO Award in History, 2018-present (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 2)
  2018 Amanda Sepp, Sarah Treadway 2019 Megan Schmucker
- Coffeehouse [Coffeehouse-Open Mic Night; The Exchange], 2013 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 2)
  [See: Oversize UPG.RG.52 Coffeehouse for Poster: "Coffeehouse Series" "Live Music at The Coffeehouse in Village Hall, Aug. 26-Nov. 18 [2013]". [Housed in Map Case]
- "College Day" [University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg "College Day"; "Kid's College"], April 12, 2002 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 2)
  Friday, April 12, 2002. Agenda. Organized by Prof. Vickilyn "Vickie" Barnot.
  For pictures see: UPG.RG.60 Visual Images. Prints. "College Day".
- Communication Through Art (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 2)
- Community Circles (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 2)
- COVID-19 Pandemic (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 2)
- Conference Place, 2000 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 2)
- Creative and Professional Writing Program [Creative Non-Fiction and Literary Festival; Creative and Professional Writing Prizes; Creative and Professional Writing Awards] (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 2)
  Student Writing Awards
- Criminal Justice Day, November 7, 2019 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 2)
  2019, Nov. 7 Legislative Action Conference
- Croquet Tournament [Greensburg Croquet Tournament; Westmoreland Croquet Tournament], 2016 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 2)
  2016. Summer. Last Croquet Tournament played on UPG Campus.
  For pictures see: UPG.RG.60 Visual Images. Prints. Croquet Tournament.
- Cultura (La), 2002-present
  - Dinner and Reception: The Life and Times of Leonardo Da Vinci, 2002 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 7, Museum-cabinet 3, Box 2, Shelf 2, Shelf 8, Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 4, Map-case 1)
    See also: UPG.RG.60 Visual Images. Ser.: Video Cassette VC III.E
    See also: UPG.RG.60 Visual Images. Ser.: Prints–Cultura (La)
    For lecture, See: UPG.RG.60 Visual Cassettes, VC VIII.15
    See also: UPG.qRG.52 Subject Files–Cultura (La) [housed in Map Case]
    See also: UPG.RG.60 Visual Images, DVD24.B.1.
  - Dinner and Reception: Paris, 2003 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 4, Map-case 1)
    See also: UPG.RG.60 Visual Images Ser.: Prints--Cultura (La) 2003 See also: UPG.qRG.52 Subject Files--Culture (La) 2003 [Poster] [housed in Map Case] See also: For Dinner and Reception, see UPG.RG.60 VC III.F and for Lecture Series, see UPG.RG.60 VC VIII.16.A-C
  - Dinner and Reception: Noche Espanola. Spain: Origins, Treasures, and Legacy of the Golden Age, 2004 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 4, Map-case 1)
    See also: UPG.qRG.52 Subject Files--Cultura, La. 2004. Poster. [housed in Map Case] See also: UPG.RG.60 Visual Images. Prints. Cultura, La. 2004. See also: UPG.RG.60 Video Cassettes. VC VIII.17.A-C.
  - Dinner and Reception: Victorian England: Empire, Evolution, and Expectations, 2005 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 4, Map-case 1)
    See also: UPG.qRG.52 Subject Files--Cultura, La. 2005. Poster. [Housed in Map Case]
  - Dinner and Reception: Classical Greece: Tradition and Challenge, 2006 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 4, Map-case 1)
    See also: UPG.qRG.52 Subject Files--Cultura, La. 2006. Poster. [housed in Map Case] See also: UPG.RG.60 Video Cassette. VC VIII.18.A-D See also: UPG.RG.60 Visual Images. Negatives. 2006, January-June. General.
  - Dinner and Reception: Welcome to China, 2007 (Map-case 1, Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 4)
    See also: UPG.RG.60 Visual Images. Prints. Cultura, La. 2007. See also: UPG.qRG.52 Subject Files—Cultura, La. 2007. [Poster] [Housed in Map Case] For lectures, See: DVD.6.A.1, DVD6.A.2
  - Dinner and Reception: Egypt: Crossroads of Civilization, 2008 (Map-case 1, Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 4)
    See also: UPG.qRG.52 Subject Files--Cultura, La. 2008. [Poster] [housed in Map Case] For lectures, See: DVD6.B
  - Dinner and Reception [La Cultura...Celebrates 45 Years of Pitt-Greensburg], 2009 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 4)
  - Dinner and Reception [La Cultura...Winter Gala: Moving Toward a Greener Future], 2010 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 4)
  - Dinner and Reception [La Cultura...Sparkling Reflections: the 10th Anniversary], January 15, 2011 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 4)
    [Note: This was the last La Cultura Dinner and Reception event. faz 1/17/12]
  - Lecture Series, 2011/2012 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 4)
    Note: This file folder contains information on the La Cultura Lecture Series beginning with the 2011/12 series and continuing onward.
    For information on the earlier lecture series, See: Cultura, La. Dinner and Reception file folders. [faz 1/26/12]
- Da Vinci Society [Da Vinci Scholars], 2001-present (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 4, Map-case 1, Box 5)
  Student honorary society launched in academic year 2001/02.
  First formal Da Vinci Scholars Induction Ceremony, December 7, 2007.
  First inductees as DaVinci Scholars (1/19/02): Dunsanee Buranathanit Erin O'Donovan Janice Roskey Sarah Tylka Tera Yingling
  2002/2003 Da Vinci Scholars: Martina Stasko, Jana Funk, Heather Weirich
  2003/2004 Da Vinci Scholars: Kellen Walsh, Kristin Verenna, Carrie Gettings, Sarah Butler, Trent Balius
  2004/2005 Da Vinci Scholars: Paul A. Rey, Carrie L. Smith, Sara L. Liberto
  2005/2006 Da Vinci Scholars: Adam Hamill, Jodi Horn, Holly Wise, Eileen Witt
  2006/2007 Da Vinci Scholars: Jonathan A. Bliss, Ellen E. Hoffman, Emily Nalevanko
  2007/2008 [Inducted Dec. 7, 2007] Amy Duli, Troy Eans, Nicole Garcher, Justin Karapindi, Megan Redfoot
  2008/2009 Kacie Frost, Amanda Jones [n.b.: Honors Convocation 2009 program lists Kacie Frost and Amanda Jones: Commencement program 2009 lists Kacie Frost, Nicole Garcher, Ellen Hoffman. For explanation of the discrepancy, e-mail from JC Biskup in file.]
  2009/2010 Samuel Emmerling; Kathryn Schreffler
  2010/2011 Monica Abdelshahid, Joyce Carson, Sean Cercone, Ngoc Lan Thiu Liu, Jennifer Shannon
  2011/2012 Sarah Carey
  2012/2013 Kendra Custer, Shawnee Fereydouni, Vanessa Malinowksi, Kayla Rodman, Wendy Wilkins
  2013/2014 Thomas Keum Crowley, Bethany Hallam, Nathan LaSor, Mavis Saadat, James Weir
  2014/2015 Ryan Brooks, Ashley Muscarella, Stephanie Russick, Emily Stark, David Tamasy, Le'Nisha Williams
  2015/2016 Stephanie Costable, Mitchell Kirk, Alexa Martin, David Postlethwait
  2016/2017 Katie Byers, Emily Frye, Nichole Johnson
  2017/2018 Alyssa Fry, Audrey Hendarsah, Amanda Sepp
  2018/2019 Madison Bredice, Jonah Jankovik, Jessica Moore
  For photographic print of first inductees, See: UPG.fRG.60 Prints--da Vinci Society--1st Induction Ceremony [Housed in Map Case]
  See also UPG.RG.60 Visual Images, Ser.: Prints--Cultura (La), 2002
  For prints of Dec. 7, 2007 Induction Ceremony, See: UPG.RG.60 Visual Images. Ser.: Prints – Da Vinci Society
  See also: UPG.RG.52 Ser.: Cultura (La), The Life and Times of Leonardo da Vinci
  See also: UPG.RG.69 Artifacts. Bas-Relief sculpture portrait--Leonardo da Vinci
- Dance Team [UPG Dance Team; UPG Bobcat Dancers] (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 5)
  For pictures, see UPG.RG.60 Visual Images--Prints.
- Dean's List (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 5)
  1980 Winter Term
  2009 Fall Term
  2010 Fall Term
  2012 Spring Term
- Digital Studies Certificate Program (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 5)
- Dr. Randi Koeske Scholarship, 2017 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 1)
  2017 Marie Miller
- Early Childhood Education Program, 2010, 2016 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 1)
  In 2010, Pitt-Greensburg received initial program approval from the Pa. Dept. of Education (PDE) to add instructional certification programs in Early Childhood Education to its curriculum. In 2016, Pitt-Greensburg received the PDE's Science, Technology, Engineering, and Mathematics (STEM) Endorsement for its Early Childhood Education Program.
- Early College Experience Program (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 1)
- Enrollment [Peoplesoft Report], 2008 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 1)
  7/21/08 Term 2087 By Campus
  7/21/08 Summer 2087 University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg
  8/25/08 Term 2091 By Campus
  8/25/08 Fall Term 2091 University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg
- Events (Campus Sponsored), 1981-present
  - African Spirits in the New World, April 9, 1999 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 1)
    A Celebration of African Religious Art and its New World Descendents. [Exhibit of the sacred art of Brazil, Haiti and Cuba; alsoincludes African and Afro-Latino music and dance. Collection of Dr. Frank S. McGlynn, Anthropologist. Reception and preview, Friday, April 9, 1999, Ferguson Theater, University of Pgh. at Greensburg] Andes Manta
  - Black History Month (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 1)
  - Children's Literature Conference, 1997-present (Map-case 1, Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 1, Box 2)
    Scope and Comtent Notes
    [1st]. May 2, 1997
    2nd, May 1, 1998 3rd, May 7, 1999
    4th, May 12, 2000
    5th, May 4, 2001
    6th, May 3, 2002
    7th, May 2, 2003
    8th, May 7, 2004
    9th, May 6, 2005
    10th, May 5, 2006
    11th, May 4, 2007
    12th, May 2, 2008
    13th, May 1. 2009
    14th, May 7, 2010
    15th, May 6, 2011
    16th, May 4, 2012
    17th, May 3, 2013
    18th, May 2, 2014
    19th, May 1, 2015
    20th, May 6, 2016
    21st, May 5, 2017
    22nd, May 4, 2018
    23rd, May 3, 2019
    24th May 1, 2020 (Cancelled due to COVID-19 Pandemic)
    For 8 illustrations on 10 sheets illustrated and signed by Steven Kellog at the 6th Children's Lit. Conf., see UPG.fRG.52 Subject Files. Ser.: Events (Campus Sponsored)
    Children's Lit. Conf., 6th, May 3, 2002. Illustrations consist of: Hannah/Bouncer/Wooster, Jenny, National Rodent Day, The Butcher's Cat from The Island of the Skog. [housed in Map File]
    [For posters, including signed posters featuring Siobhan Vivian and Brian Pinkne, See: Oversize UPG.fRG.52 Subject Files Ser.: Events (Campus sponsored) Children's Lit. Conf. 5/3/13) [in Map Case]]
    [For posters, including signed posters featuring Steven Sheinkin and John Rocco, See: Oversize UPG.fRG.52 Subject Files Ser.: Events (Campus Sponsored) Children's Lit. Conf. 18th May 2, 2014 [in Map Case]]
    [For posters, including signed poster featuring Marc Tyler Nobleman, See: Oversize UPG.fRG.52 Subject Files. Ser.: Events (Campus Sponsored) Children's Lit. Conf. 19th, May 1, 2015. In Map Case.] [n.b.: FF contains a CD of photographs of the 2015 Children's Literature Conference.][n.b.: FF also contains a CD of M.T. Nobleman's Session: Heroes With and Without Capes.]
    [n.b.: FF contains a sample of the "Lunch Bag" given out to attendees as a memento of the 20th anniversary of the Children's Lit. Conference.] [For posters including signed copies by Jack Gantos and Paul O. Zalinsky, See: Oversize UPG.fRG.52 Subject Files. Ser.: Events (Campus Sponsored) Children's Lit. Conf., 20th, May 6, 2016 [Housed in Map Case].]
    [For posters including signed copies of featured speakers, Jay Asher and Suzanne Bloom, See: Oversize UPG.RG.52 Subject Files. Ser.: Events (Campus Sponsored) Children's Lit. Conf., May 5, 2017 [Housed in Map Case])
    [For posters of featured speakers A.S. King and signed poster of Mark Weakland, See: Oversize UPG.RG.52 Subject Files. Ser.: Events (Campus Sponsored) Children's Literature Conference 22nd, May 4, 2018. Housed in Map Case.]
    [For posters of featured speakers, Ellen Oh and Jonathan Gottschall and poster "Morning Breakout Session Details", "Afternoon Breakout Session Details". See: Oversize UPG.RG.52 Subject Files. Ser.: Events (Campus Sponsored) Children's Literature Conference, 23rd, May 3, 2019.
  - German Christmas Festival, 1981 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 2)
  - Hispanic Heritage Celebration, Sept. 18-Oct. 12, 1998 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 2)
    "Portraits of the Andes", an exhibit of watercolor art by award winning artist Victor Beltran, Sept. 18-Oct. 12, 1998 (poster).
  - Humanities Day [Pitt-Greensburg Humanities Day], 1982-1998, 2016 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 2)
    Note: first Humanities Day was organized by Dr. Colette Levin in 1982. 1982-1998 as Humanities Day hiatus, 1999-2015 2016, May 7. Pitt-Greensburg Humanities Day.
    For DVD of 2016 Humanities Day address by Keynote Speaker, David Conrad, See: UPG.RG.60 DVD34. (For video cassettes: 1983, 1984, 1991, 1992, 1993, 1994, 1995, 1996, 1997, 1998. See UPG.RG.60 VC III.B.1-12.) (For DVD format: 1983, 1996, 1997, SEE: DVD24.B.3 1983 Track 1,2; 1996 (Track 3), 1997 (Track 4); 2016 (DVD34)
  - Invisible Made Visible: The Angels from the Vatican, April 10, 1999 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 2)
  - Ohio Country Conference, May 24-25, 2001 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 2)
    6th Annual, May 24-25, 2001: "Archaeology and the Wars for Empire: 1754-1794".
  - Science Day (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 2)
  - Various: High School Accounting Career Day, October 28, 2016 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 2)
- Exhibits, 1998-2010 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 3)
  1998, Sept. 18-Oct. 12. Portraits of the Andes
  1999, Jan. 26-Feb. 26. Thaddeus Mosley Art Exhibit
  1999, Apr. 9. African Spirits in the New World. Collection of Frank S. McGlynn.
  2000, Sept. 16-Oct. 7. Mexican Artisans in residence.
  2000, Sept. 22. Metamorphosis. An Art Exhibition by Constance Sturm.
  2001, Jan. 29-Feb. 2. Condemned: Inside the Sing Sing Death House. Curated by Scott Christianson, Ph.D., Director, New York Death Penalty Documentation Project.
  2001, Mar. Mary Baker Eddy Exhibit [Women's History Month 2001]
  2002, Nov. The Green Edge of Westmoreland.
  2004, Mar. "Spirit of Color". Exhibit of works by Reuben Alfonso Lopez Nieto. [In Millstein Lib.]
  2005, April "Dos Mundos". The Photography of David Farmerie.
  2010, Sept. 7-Oct. 14 "I Thought I Could Fly", an exhibit of photographs by Charlee Brodsky.
- Faculty Fight Club, September 2019 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 3)
  1st [Round 1] Sept. 9, 2019; Round 2, Sept. 25, 2019
- Faculty Recognition Display and Reception, 2018-Present (Map-case 1, Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 4)
  Historical Note: The initial Pitt-Greensburg Faculty Scholarship Recognition Event, sponsored by the Millstein Library, took place on Sept. 20, 2018. The event highlighted: Posters identifying faculty: Publications; Presentations; Grants, Stipends, Professional Service, Community Service, CFAR (Center for Applied Research) affiliation participation. Included in the UPG Archives is a listing (with copies, summaries, extracts or briefs) of publications by faculty members in the Humanities and Natural Science Divisions.
  2018, Sept. 20
  2019, Sept. 24
  2021, Sept. 23
  2023, Apr. 21, Sept. 21
  n.b.: Posters housed in Map Case. UPG.qRG.52 Ser.: Faculty Recognition Display and Reception.
- Faculty/Staff vs. Students Charity Basketball Game, Annual, 2010-present (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 3)
  2nd, March 23, 2010
  4th, April 2, 2012
  5th, March 21, 2013
  6th, March 28, 2014
  7th, April 2, 2015
  [11th] April, 8, 2019
- Faculty/Staff vs. Students Charitable Volleyball Game, 2017-2018 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 3)
  2017, April 4 2018, April 5
- Faculty Workshop, 2015 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 3)
  Contents: Summer 2015 Workshop Schedule
- Flag Pavilion [Flag Plaza] (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 3)
- Flood [Tropical Storm Gordon, 2018], September 8-10, 2018 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 4, Box 2)
  UPG Campus flood which resulted from a total of 8.65 inches of rainfall over the Greensburg area in a 72 hour period [Sept. 8-10] from remnants of Tropical Storm Gordon. [Pictures taken by Diane Hughes 9/10/2018, 11:15 a.m.]
- Formal Poetry Night (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 3)
- Fortieth Anniversary [40th UPG Anniversary], 2003 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 3)
  See: UPG.RG.60 History. Anniveraries. 40th, 2003.
- Forty Fifth Anniversary [45th UPG Anniversary], 2008 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 3)
  See: UPG.RG.60 History. Anniversaries. 45th, 2008.
- Founder's Day at Pitt-Greensburg, October 10, 2016 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 3)
- Gerontology Certificate Program (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 3)
- Gimbel Pennsylvania Art Collection, 1958-1988 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 6, Box 5, Map-case 1)
  [See also: UPG.RG.02.2 Series IV Memoranda. Memoranda dtd Feb. 25, 1988, E. McCord to provost Weingartner with FYI to Pres. George F. Chambers.]
  The exhibition of the Gimbel Pa. Art Collection, that part of which consisted primarily of works dealing with Western Pennsylvania and which was given to the University of Pittsburgh in 1959 by Gimbel Brothers, Inc., was mounted in recognition of the University of Pittsburgh's Bicentennial in 1987.